Nick Jacob

Front-End Web Developer

Woodland Hills, CA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Nick-Jacob/5f376307b45fcb6e

Nick started his professional career as a computer graphics designer in the video game industry. Eventually, he transitioned into the business side of the industry where he represented multiple design studios and negotiated contracts on their behalf.

Over time, Nick fell in love with web development and decided to leave the video game industry to embark on a new career as a Front-end Web Developer. Nick is an expert at developing and designing user-focused websites and web applications. When he's not working, Nick enjoys...Nick is always working.

Willing to relocate to: Los Angeles, CA

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Programmer / Analyst

UCLA - DAVID GEFFEN SCHOOL OF MEDICINE - Westwood, CA - March 2017 to Present

Westwood, CA (contract assignment) March 2017 - Present

Computing Technologies Research Laboratory (CTRL) is a UCLA sales & service entity focused on software development

Programmer / Analyst

- * UI/UX, jQuery, JavaScript, HTML 5, CSS 3
- * Bootstrap, responsive design
- * Content migration, data analysis

Web Designer / Developer

NSJ DESIGN - Woodland Hills, CA - September 2013 to Present

Woodland Hills, CA September 2013 - Present

NSJ Design is a web design company that specializes in building websites with WordPress

Web Designer / Developer

- * WordPress web design and development
- * UI/UX, jQuery, JavaScript, HTML 5, CSS 3
- * Bootstrap, responsive design

Web Designer / Contractor

BEHLA DESIGN + DEVELOPMENT - Woodland Hills, CA - November 2014 to March 2016

Woodland Hills, CA November 2014 - March 2016

Behla Design + Development is a web design company that specializes in building websites with WordPress Web Designer / Contractor

- * WordPress web design and development
- * Social media management
- * Project management

Consultant / Contractor

BROADBANDTV CORP - Vancouver, BC - June 2013 to August 2013

Vancouver, Canada (contract assignment) June 2013 - August 2013

BroadbandTV Corp is a social media company that generates advertising revenue for content creators on YouTube

Consultant / Contractor

Consultant / Contractor

INTERACTIVE STUDIO MANAGEMENT - Sacramento, CA - June 2012 to October 2012

Sacramento, CA (contract assignment) June 2012 - October 2012

ISM is an agency representing the business interests of software development companies to the video game publishing community

Consultant / Contractor

Business Development Manager

ORIGINAL FORCE - Nanjing, CN - April 2011 to March 2012

Nanjing, China April 2011 - March 2012

Original Force is a top China-based contractor for computer graphics services in the entertainment industry Business Development Manager

- * Expanded international customer base
- * Account manager for several large corporate customers

Agent / Owner

NICK JACOB AGENCY - Camarillo, CA - January 2009 to March 2011

Camarillo, CA January 2009 - March 2011

NJA was an agency that represented computer graphics studios and software development companies Agent / Owner

- * Represented international computer graphics firms
- * Placed clients on high profile projects

Consultant / Contractor

INTERACTIVE STUDIO MANAGEMENT - Sacramento, CA - June 2005 to December 2008

Sacramento, CA June 2005 - December 2008

ISM is an agency representing the business interests of software development companies to the video game publishing community

Consultant / Contractor

EDUCATION

BS in Business

California State Channel Islands 2005

SKILLS

Bootstrap (4 years), CSS (4 years), HTML (4 years), JavaScript (4 years), jQuery (4 years)

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Skills

See my website for a portfolio and additional information: https://www.nsjdesign.com/

 $\sqrt{\text{HTML 5}}$, CSS 3, JavaScript, jQuery, PHP, MySQL, Git, Bootstrap, WordPress, Adobe Creative Suite, User Interface Design, User Experience Design

 $\sqrt{}$ Outstanding written and verbal communication skills for communicating with teammates, writing emails and creating powerful presentations

√ Excellent references supplied upon request